<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<modules><module><id><![CDATA[42]]></id><name><![CDATA[leguide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LeGuide.com]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers. It is&nbsp;a fantastic window for e-merchants!      The LeGuide.com Group is the number 1 independent French publisher of shopping guides, shopping-based search engines and price comparison on the internet. It already exists in 14 countries and 9 different languages.  LeGuide.com has been a trusted partner of shoppers and merchants since 1998: the former, it helps to find the most interesting product offers online and the latter it helps in improving their visibility and developing their operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module gives you the opportunity to develop your business and highlight your site your best deals!    When you sell products online, it&rsquo;s essential that potential customers can find their way to your site. Whether they are trying to unearth a particular product or are simply trying to find the cheapest offer, buyers are using shopping guides more and more; having a listing on a price comparison website is therefore vital if you want to make yourself known to millions of buyers about to make a purchase and thus boost your sales.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[88]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/42.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/42-leguidecom.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[213]]></id><name><![CDATA[allexport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Export orders / customers / catalog]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[The Export Orders / Customers / Catalog module helps you to save time by displaying a summary of all orders placed through your store, registered customers and your catalog]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[The Export Orders / Customers / Catalog module helps you to save time by displaying a summary of all orders placed through your store, registered customers and your catalog.  Thanks to the Export Orders / Customers / Catalog module, export data from your orders, your customers and your catalog directly into a spreadsheet.  Use all your data with your accounting or order-picking for example.    The data that will be exported are:  The number of orders  The clients’ names  The clients’ first names  The customer's billing addresses  The client’s delivery address  The email  The order status  The Order date the Payment method  The discount  The total paid  The total actually paid  The total without taxes  Total income  Packaging  Products ordered    To extract exactly what you want you will have several options, firstly you can sort by date but also by status, whether for all your orders, those that were paid or those waiting.  The export file is done under the. CSV format, which you can open with many programs, including Microsoft Excel or OpenOffice.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Axome]]></author><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[29]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/213.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[90]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/export-modules/213-export-orders-customers-catalog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[367]]></id><name><![CDATA[banipmod]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ban IP addresses]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Are spammers and fraudulent transactions affecting your revenue?   Ban their IP address to restrict their access to your online store]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Are spammers and fraudulent transactions affecting your revenue?   Ban their IP address to restrict their access to your online store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Choose between redirecting them to another website or allowing them to browse but denying them access to make purchases.  Stop wasting time and money by banning unreliable customers.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[17]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/367.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/367-ban-ip-addresses.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click    Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously?  It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!    Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.    A precious additional sales tool    Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do.  Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.    Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.    Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited.  Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.    Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack?  That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!    Integrated assistant    It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem.  When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock.  There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.    Remain the maestro of combinations    One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set?  Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.    You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.    Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.    Business Incentive    Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction.  Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers?  All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost!  Stop looking, you have already found the solution !    To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.    3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;     Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the pack   Apply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of products   Apply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example      Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack.  This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.    You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore    Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!    Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.    By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up.  Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.    In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.    Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.    Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!    For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities.  Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.    For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !    Highlight your packs and sell more    Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...    For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs.  Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.    And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots  This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!    We don&#39;t forget designers    From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator.  The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.    A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[33]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.1]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[269.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstracking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[UPS, the #1 package delivery service in the United States, is a key player in ecommerce]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[UPS, the #1 package delivery service in the United States, is a key player in ecommerce. Offering UPS as a form of delivery is crucial for customers looking for speedy, tracked and dependable delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[18]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.8]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Easily export your entire product catalog to Google Shopping, the new Google developed price comparison service!    Note: A subscription to a third party service is required in order to use the module]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Easily export your entire product catalog to Google Shopping, the new Google developed price comparison service!    Note: A subscription to a third party service is required in order to use the module.  Please subscribe to the service before making this purchase.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Product Listing Ads drive traffic and sales to your website or local store by showing online shoppers rich images and details of items you sell.    Product Listing Ads appear when someone searches for your products on google.com and google.com/shopping. Customers who click on your ad will be directed to your website where they can buy your item.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[113]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.7]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/1615-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2191]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestanotify]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Box Notification (Popup)]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Sale more with this module!  Merchants often need to put forward a possible warning, a call to action or just a greeting!  With this module, inform your customers of a flash sale, of sales, promotions]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Sale more with this module!  Merchants often need to put forward a possible warning, a call to action or just a greeting!  With this module, inform your customers of a flash sale, of sales, promotions, and guide them on their arrival in your online shop.  Very easy to use: you only have one image or text to add, create a link on the page a match, and you make additional sales in the category of your choice.  ﻿]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Box Notification helps you to increase your sales!]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[93]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2191.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/2191-box-notification-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2375]]></id><name><![CDATA[vente_flash]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Flash sale Pro / Doorbuster]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Boost your online store sales with the PrestaShop Flash Sales / Door Buster Pro module!  The updated version of this innovative module lets you offer special sales to your customers through customized]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Boost your online store sales with the PrestaShop Flash Sales / Door Buster Pro module!  The updated version of this innovative module lets you offer special sales to your customers through customized flash (door buster) sales!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.3]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[122]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.1]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2375.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/2375-flash-sale-v2-doorbuster.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world’s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.    Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.    The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.    Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.    This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons  since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.158]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[293]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Provide to your customers the products that meet their needs.    Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products,&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;can add as many search engines as you want and place them in different places on your website.  This module was developed in an effort to provide short loading times, even on large catalogs.  Your visitors can browse products that match their search criteria, to make their purchases in minimal time.    Winner of the Best PrestaShop Modules Awards 2012    Advanced Search 4 won the&nbsp;Best module&nbsp;of the year Award at the PrestaShop BarCamp of Barcelona (Spain)!    Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products.    Advanced Search 4&nbsp;adds the multi-layered navigation, search by step, filters and multi-criteria searches.  Each search is saved over the navigation, allowing your visitors to return to the results of their research at any time.    Google is his friend    This PrestaShop Addon is a small revolution for SEO. Advanced Search 4 generate a mass-produced products pages optimized for SEO, and without duplicate content!  Pick up your criteria on which you want to improve your SEO, validate them, and here you go with hundreds of pages listing your products, including: re-written URL, H1 tags, description, meta tags, automatised cross links...&nbsp;    To maximize your reputation, these results pages can be shared on most social networks places around the internet, as well as sent by e-mail.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.10.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[154]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/search-filters-prestashop-modules/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!  You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!  You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time!  In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category.  Look for products that you want to add this category and add 1 click!  You also control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.11]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[30]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/bulk-update-prestashop-modules/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[none]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently !  Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating dail]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently !  Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily tasks&nbsp;and making it simple to update your shop.  &nbsp;  Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management.  Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.  Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!  &nbsp;  *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***    ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.  Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!  &nbsp;  Spend an Hour, Save a Day!  Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds.  For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you.  &nbsp;  Take Your Online Business to the Bank  Buy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules.  Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks.  &nbsp;Benefit initially from 30-day free trial!  &nbsp;]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.12.0.800]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[3]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.7]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3052]]></id><name><![CDATA[wordpresssync]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[WordPress Sync]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Make your blog and extension of your e-store with PrestaShop's WordPress Sync module!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Make your blog and extension of your e-store with PrestaShop's WordPress Sync module!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.6.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[69]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3052.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/content-management/3052-wordpress-sync.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3162]]></id><name><![CDATA[webcallback]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Call Back]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!   Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!   Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold. Stop wasting customers&rsquo; time with the Call Back Module. Let customers leave their contact information for you to contact them at a convenient time. Capture customers you would have otherwise lost.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[40]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3162.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3162-web-call-back.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Save time during your shipping process by mass printing labels! The Print Shipping Labels Pro Module lets you add fields in bulk to shipping labels to optimize printing jobs]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Save time during your shipping process by mass printing labels! The Print Shipping Labels Pro Module lets you add fields in bulk to shipping labels to optimize printing jobs.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[125]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don't have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it's not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[34]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.6]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[3511]]></id><name><![CDATA[priceminister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PriceMinister]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the PriceMinister for Prestashop module, your processing is automated, the products are exported directly to the PriceMinister marketplace and your orders are automatically imported and integrated into your Prestashop store.      You also automate communication with your customers: your order confirmations are sent directly to the customer by email via the PriceMinister web service, customers are automatically notified and the status of your orders is automatically updated.    By using the PriceMinister module, you maintain control of your offer and product flows, you automatically import your orders without additional cost or subscription and your data exchanges are automated and free.    Integration is easy and convenient: you configure your module, your export becomes automatic and so you have no more data to manipulate    Implementing scheduled tasks is simple and automated thanks to compatibility with the Prestashop Cron task-scheduling editor module (free). Just click on a button to automatically integrate your scheduled tasks in the module. It is still possible to manually configure your tasks.    The module design is based on the online merchant experience. The module was conceived by an online merchant in the service of his colleagues and developed by professional developers, which gives it ease of use and maximum effectiveness.    Your purchase is protected by free technical support which is assured unconditionally up to the moment of making the products available online and the import of your first orders.    You must have a PriceMinister PRO account.    New version, PriceMinister v4: export XML, simplified configuration, native scheduled tasks, intelligent mapping, sleek design and improved ergonomics.    This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.07]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[64]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3511.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[244.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[144.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/3511-priceminister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3559]]></id><name><![CDATA[privatesale]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Private Sales PrestaShop]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Give customers preferential treatment while clearing out old inventory with the Private Sales module! Get started today to start creating and running private sales]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Give customers preferential treatment while clearing out old inventory with the Private Sales module! Get started today to start creating and running private sales.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The Private Sales Module allows you to:     Give specific customers (VIP&rsquo;s) premier status and access to sales   Build customer loyalty with preferential treatment   Attract new customers with the latest ecommerce selling model   Specify particular products to feature to clear out old inventory      The Private Sales Module is easy to use.  Configure the module with these steps:     Name your Private Sale   Upload an image   Write a description   List the categories (e.g. product type, brand, size, children, etc.)   List the customer groups that the private sale is open to (registered visitors, customers, VIP, etc.)   Duration: set the time and date for both the beginning and ending of the sale    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[53]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3559.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3559-private-sales-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[3634]]></id><name><![CDATA[jcaccountgroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Account Group]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Account Group module allow your customers to create their account directly into a choosen group, and to moderate or not the subscription according to the group]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Account Group module allow your customers to create their account directly into a choosen group, and to moderate or not the subscription according to the group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Account Group module allow your customers to create an account directly into a particular group.  In fact, if your site uses the concept of user groups (professionals, retailers, students, ...), you no longer have to create the account manually, or worse, let your customer order with the wrong pricing before changing its group status.  For each group, you can choose whether or not it is enabled by default. If it is activated directly, then the process is the same as usual (no mail sent to the client, but the administrator can receive an email).  If you need to verify the information before activating the account, then a mail is sent to the customer following the creation of the account (a message also appears on the screen). In this email, you can add a message (customizable for each group) to explain the possible things to do (send a copy of a professional card, student card, ...).  At the same time, you receive an email telling you that a new account has been created and is awaiting moderation. A full summary of the account (address included) is included in the email.  Links let you activate directly the account, or visit the page dedicated to pending accounts.  This page shows the list of accounts awaiting validation. For each account, full details of the account is displayed, and a set of buttons allow you to validate or refuse the account, to see the administration page of the account, to contact the person via email.  If you activate a customer account, a confirmation email is sent to the customer indicating that he can now order on your site.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.8]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[34]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3634.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3634-account-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation FB]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more.  Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !    This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[58]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.9]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[4549]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmurealtimestats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Real Time Statistics]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !  With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !  With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module lets you know exactly what is happening on your shop.  Now you are able to visualize the path of a visitor, his reactions on each page visited, ease or blocking steps in the ordering process ...   ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.11]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[15]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.7]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4549.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/4549-dmu-real-time-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4556]]></id><name><![CDATA[innovativemenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Rich menu]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create and effectively manage menu and navigation bars with the Rich Menu Module developed by PrestaShop!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create and effectively manage menu and navigation bars with the Rich Menu Module developed by PrestaShop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this module, create interactive menus with endless features.  This module includes 150+ built in features to help you create a navigation menus that suits your online store&rsquo;s needs.  Increase profits through advertisements embedded in each category.  Give categories and products more visibility while simplifying the user experience to increase your conversion rate!]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.16]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[236]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.5]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4556.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/4556-rich-menu.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4780]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushslide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider and Push products - 2 in 1]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[  Increase drastically the visibility of your chosen products or offers thanks to the module Slider &amp; Push Products developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;﻿      Change the appearance of your online shop i]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[  Increase drastically the visibility of your chosen products or offers thanks to the module Slider &amp; Push Products developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;﻿      Change the appearance of your online shop in a few clicks and give it a professional look. Boost your online shop, make all your promotions successful, increase the visibility of your chosen products and sell more!﻿  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[2-in-1, you will be able to add a slideshow as well as a push products in your online store. You can choose between 9 templates to entirely customize your website and give it a professional look. Furthermore, you can adapt your homepage according to the native language of each of your customers!﻿]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[78]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4780.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/4780-slider-push-products-2-in-1.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4932]]></id><name><![CDATA[mynewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter & Statistics]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- a]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- and help keep them coming back to shop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Track the effectiveness of each newsletter. Every KPI you, as an online merchant, should monitor is available at your fingertips. These key statistics allow online merchants to monitor newsletters to see which work and which don&rsquo;t to improve newsletter mailings.    Additional benefits include:     Inform customers about sales, company or industry news, new products, etc.   Personalize newsletters (to echo your brand identity)   Build customer loyalty to your brand   Stay in touch with your customers    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.22]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[197]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4932.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4932-newsletter-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO    Internal linking&nbsp;is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a&nbsp;better place on Google.    To&nbsp;optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an&nbsp;internal linking&nbsp;that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.    SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your&nbsp;SEO strategy.    Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!    If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module&nbsp;HTML On Descriptions.    Do we really need internal linking?    Internal linking strategy&nbsp;based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.    Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to&nbsp;follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.    With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.    It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners.  SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.1.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[19]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop&#39;s and products&#39; profitability !    The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly,&nbsp;profit and profit margin.    Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like &quot;what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?&quot;.    This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV&nbsp;file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.    This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.      You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.2.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[45]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5275]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbycategoryslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products of same category]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to make cross-selling of other products in each category, and increase your average shopping basket.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[24]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5275.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/5275-slider-products-of-same-category.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5277]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbybrandslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products by brand]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Let customers discover other products by the same brand, thanks to the slider at the bottom of your product pages! This module will increase your average cart by sharing products from a brand your cus]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Let customers discover other products by the same brand, thanks to the slider at the bottom of your product pages! This module will increase your average cart by sharing products from a brand your customers already like. This easy to configure module will enhance the look of your site and appeal to your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Easily add cross selling strategies used by e-commerce giants to your online shop.  Share products from the same brand to encourage customers to purchase more!  This slider also increases visibility of other products that your customers may not have seen otherwise! Boost sales easily and add additional value to every one of your product pages.﻿]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[15]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5277.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/5277-slider-products-by-brand.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5476]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MailChimp - 1.4 & 1.5]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[The MailChimp module gives you access to amazing features that help you design, share and publish customized newsletter campaigns]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[The MailChimp module gives you access to amazing features that help you design, share and publish customized newsletter campaigns.  Track the results of your newsletter campaigns to see how well they work! It&rsquo;s like having your own personal publishing platform installed in your ecommerce store!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[45]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[5.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5476.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/5476-mailchimp.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[5542]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy order preparation]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Efficiently run your online store&rsquo;s operations with the Product Locator for warehouses module!   This module allows you export warehouse locations of each product by order number and product qua]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Efficiently run your online store&rsquo;s operations with the Product Locator for warehouses module!   This module allows you export warehouse locations of each product by order number and product quantity. After you&rsquo;ve exported the data, sort by it by quantity, supplier, warehouse location or product ID to expedite the picking process.    Save time precious processing time with this module!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[20]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5542.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/5542-easy-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders.  Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le March&eacute; is one of France&rsquo;s leading marketplaces.    Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success:  - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount)  - multiple delivery methods, etc.    Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.    1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices.  In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products:  - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace,  - Prices and inventories are automatically updated,  - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.    Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.    A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module&rsquo;s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants&nbsp;for the benefit of fellow e-merchants&nbsp;and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.    Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.      *This offer applies for merchants already registered on&nbsp;CleMarch&eacute;&nbsp;Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with&nbsp;any other ongoing&nbsp;Cdiscount.com&nbsp;offer.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.68]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[101]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[194.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[8]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[6320]]></id><name><![CDATA[totshowmailalerts]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product out of stock : emails and number of requests]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[The module will allow you to know how many customers are waiting for a product and to obtain your customers mail address who wishes to receive an alert when a product will be out of stock]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[The module will allow you to know how many customers are waiting for a product and to obtain your customers mail address who wishes to receive an alert when a product will be out of stock.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[If you have a product out of stock, the module "Alert mail" from PrestaShop allows you to collect address mails without knowing how many times your product is solicited and who have wanted to order.  With the module ”Product out of stock : emails and number of requests”, you can get:  -    The number of request by product,  -    Customer emails address.  Optimize your suppliers orders and thank to the product quantity praised, improve your restocking.  During out of stock, obtain a maximum of email address and identify the expectations of your customers according to the different articles for a better inventory management.  Allow your customers to be advised on the renewal of your stock to let them come back again in your shop.   ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[202 ecommerce]]></author><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.11]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[19]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6320.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/6320-product-out-of-stock-emails-and-number-of-requests.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!    With&nbsp;Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!    If you also use our layered navigation system&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;(Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.    Customer study :    Ocarat.com: &quot;Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can&#39;t assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds.&nbsp;Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !&quot;]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[47]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/search-filters-prestashop-modules/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6413]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_cachemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cache Manager]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate and SEO    The statistics are clear: the main reason why a user leave a web page is the loading time.    Yahoo! said that adding 400ms to the page loading time on their car website raises the dropout rate from 5 to 9%. (Sources: Performance Web)    In addition, the speed display is a guarantee of quality which has a very positive influence on the positioning in the search engines.    Let your customers enjoy a more comfortable navigation on your website by shortening the loading time of pages, and saving his time!    Limited offer : Price drop &amp; Satisfied or refunded !]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[20]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.6]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6413.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/6413-cache-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6414]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgabonos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Credit Notes / Memos - Cancellation of Invoices]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create full credit notes / memos for any invoice you need to cancel. Issue the notes in PDF and send them to your clients]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create full credit notes / memos for any invoice you need to cancel. Issue the notes in PDF and send them to your clients.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to create full credit notes for any invoices that have been issued and then cancelled.    With this module, you can issue credit notes by selecting the invoice you want to refund. It only works with issued invoices.    No more problems with invoices and journal entries. With this module, you avoid submitting invoices that have been cancelled.    You can also issue credit notes in PDF and send them to your clients.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[12]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6414.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/billing-invoicing-prestashop-modules/6414-credit-notes-memos-cancellation-of-invoices.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[7152]]></id><name><![CDATA[customfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Fields]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[It's important to know about as much as possible about customers. It will help with better understanding of the clients habits and needs. That knowledge will allow e-merchant to improve it's services and finally make more profit of his business. Custom fields module in easy way allows you to create unlimited number of custom fields and get all required data about your customers that cannot be done with standard registration form. All fields can be validated with selected validation rule and can be viewed and editable in the backoffice.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[30]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.5]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7152.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/content-management/7152-custom-fields.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[7287]]></id><name><![CDATA[olark]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Olark]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Use your favorite IM client to enhance relationships with customers, see detailed activities, and accordingly increase your sales]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Use your favorite IM client to enhance relationships with customers, see detailed activities, and accordingly increase your sales. The Olark module grants all of these wishes, all within your IM client!﻿  &nbsp;  Currently serving both large and small organizations across the world, Olark is a simple, yet effective service. By installing the module, you can monitor all visitors&#39; activities on your store and then proactively chat with them, all within your IM client. Don&#39;t worry about downloading a foreign IM client that you don&#39;t know how to use&mdash;Olark is compatible with any chat client that supports Jabber/XMPP or Gtalk; so go ahead, use your Gmail!    The chat box that customers use is completely customizable to fit your store&#39;s themes and styles. Also, the chat box has the capability to remain open during browsing. This means that customers will be able to chat with you AND add items to their cart, all at the same time; absolutely no sales lost. Any inquiry can be immediately responded to, right on the spot! Your customers will appreciate the customized attention they receive.  &nbsp;  Don&#39;t let your customers wander aimlessly around your store anymore! Answer questions proactively and efficiently and see an increase in your sales in no time!﻿  &nbsp;  Create a Free account with Olark now!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[10]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.8]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7287.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[69.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/7287-olark.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price increment/discount by customer groups]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[   Apply different price to&nbsp;the product&nbsp;depending on the group that customer belongs to   Apply a markup to your products    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[8]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/7422-price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[8244]]></id><name><![CDATA[ec_seo404]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO - disabled and deleted 301 redirect Products]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product. You will be able to choose for each case a 301 (Ideal for SEO)]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Whenever a product is disabled or deleted, you will be able to assign a 301 redirect.  No need to turn your catalog to find out which product is not active or has been removed, you can see them with the module and react accordingly.  Not overload your HTACCESS file and therefore no notion necessary to make it work !  The SEO which existed to this product will be redirected in confidence to a similar product, category page, etc. ... And not lose all the SEO that page had.  With a color scheme, get in a glance the status of your references:  - Green =&gt; Redirection possible for disabled or deleted products, but the redirection is not active. - Orange =&gt; Redirection possible for disabled or deleted products, but the redirection is not active and no link is specified for the redirection. - Red =&gt; Redirection enabled, but no link! So page 404 as usual!]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Ether Création]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.13]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[12]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.3]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8244.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/8244-seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[8458]]></id><name><![CDATA[wic_pushproductcms]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push Products on CMS Pages]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages.  Use all the pages of your website and increase your sales!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module oriented Merchandising allows you to optimize all your pages, including these you thought it was not possible (Shipping, Secure Payment, Legals, etc..)       Highlight a selection of products on your CMS pages.   Configure these products by CMS pages directly from your back office easely.   Increase your sales.    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Web In Color]]></author><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.11]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[6]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.2]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8458.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/8458-push-products-on-cms-pages.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[THE ONLY MODULE THAT ALLOWS YOU TO FULLY COMPLY WITH THE EU COOKIE LAW]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[THE ONLY MODULE THAT ALLOWS YOU TO FULLY COMPLY WITH THE EU COOKIE LAW. Display a responsive and customized warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.    Complete compliance with the law    Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."    Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.    Main features of the modules       Display a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consent   Disable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.   Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.   Fully customize the warning banner (colour, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency...)      Getting the user consent     The module includes 3 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:     Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled.   Acceptance through the navigation (with banner disappearance): If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.   Acceptance through the navigation (without banner disappearance) : If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. Works the same as the previous option except the fact that the banner is always displayed and never disappears. The selected cookies will be disabled when users enter the store and will get enabled only when users will decide to go another page.    Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)    Customizing the banner content and design    As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).    The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, colour, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background colour of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is mutlilingual and automatially detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.    Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots cawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.    Disabling the modules that use cookies    This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookied on their computer with their consent.    "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law    To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.    Multistore mode    The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.5.6.3]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[121]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Push on Cart module:     Easily increase your customer&rsquo;s average cart value   Clear unsold products from your inventory   Get your customers to discover new products to create a need and even secure their loyalty   Create demand for new products   Capitalize on impulse purchases   Improve customer satisfaction and loyalty with customized discounts on select products    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[23]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[3.4]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/11345-push-on-cart.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[15611]]></id><name><![CDATA[ezakorecopack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pack E-merchandising 1to1 par Ezako]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Stop displaying bikinis when your visitor is looking for skis ! Cross-Sell, Up-Sell and Personalized Product Recommendations for Home, Product and Basket pages]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Stop displaying bikinis when your visitor is looking for skis ! Cross-Sell, Up-Sell and Personalized Product Recommendations for Home, Product and Basket pages.  &nbsp;  Start now&nbsp;to enjoy your one month free trial period !  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[EZAKO recommends products specially chosen to please each of your customers individually. We are available for Prestashop versions 1.4, 1.5 and 1.6. &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Sales  &nbsp;     Up to 24,75% of increase of your average basket size   33% of increase of your conversion rate   Up to 41% of direct impact on your sales    &nbsp;  One-to-one E-merchandising  &nbsp;     3 minutes to personalize your E-merchandising   Cross-Sell, Up-Sell, Clearance, Promotions &hellip; Mix them all !   Give strength to your existing marketing strategies and create new ones with our conversion dashboards by product, brand and category    &nbsp;  Technology  &nbsp;     3 years of R&amp;D so that you won&rsquo;t have to do it yourself   Be part of the Big Data in Real Time experience !    &nbsp;  Pricing  &nbsp;     Try our solution for free - one month   Monthly subscription, starting at 89&euro;   No strings attached        Start now&nbsp;to enjoy your one month free trial period !  ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.6]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[0]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[0.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/15611.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/15611-ezako-reco-pack-cross-sell-up-sell-down-sell.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!    This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for bette]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!    This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better visibility on search engines and social media platforms.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatically create meta tags to save over 40 hours!  With the SEO Expert module:     Appear on first page results on search engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.   Multiply your sales with increased web traffic   Improve visibility for each language of your store   Increase your conversions with qualified traffic   Differentiate your store with fully customized rules for product and category pages   Leverage Facebook and Twitter to acquire even more customers   Optimize your online store for social media with adapted shared titles    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.23]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[61]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[4.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[219.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/seo-prestashop-modules/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[16947]]></id><name><![CDATA[shopymind]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[ShopyMind - Abandoned cart reminder]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Automate your email campaigns and marketing actions: recover&nbsp;abandoned carts, reward your best customers, send them birthday wishes, and follow the performances to increase your conversion rate]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Automate your email campaigns and marketing actions: recover&nbsp;abandoned carts, reward your best customers, send them birthday wishes, and follow the performances to increase your conversion rate.  &nbsp;  Try our offer now for free and get &euro; 250!  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[An account must be created and a commitment-free subscription taken out to use the ShopyMind module.    &nbsp;  Automate your marketing actions    ShopyMind provides you with a set of predefined campaigns that you can use individually or in combination.  Once your campaigns have been defined, ShopyMind will automatically apply them for you, thus saving you time that you can then dedicate to your core business activity.    Increase your conversion rate    As you are perhaps already aware, email marketing is one of the most important tools to use where conversion rates are concerned.  Based on this observation and armed with the experience we have in this area, we at ShopyMind decided we wanted to make simple and effective e-marketing tools available to e-businesses.  Use our tools to create and manage your email marketing campaigns. By doing so you will maximize your chances of attracting and converting your visitors and building their loyalty.    Build customer loyalty    Building customer loyalty no doubt forms part of your e-business strategy, and this is something we understand.  ShopyMind is a powerful customer relationship management tool (CRM): profiling, personalized suggestions tailored to the customer&#39;s buying profile, exclusive offers, and social networks are all methods available for you to use to make your e-business a success story!    Track and optimize your sales    ShopyMind records the key indicators for your campaigns in real-time.  This means that the view, click and conversion rates and turnover figures generated by our system can be identified in your statistical reports.  Each report can be segmented by country, language and campaign type to enable you to sell more effectively and to target sales to the profiles of each and every one of your customers.  &nbsp;    Try our offer now for free and get &euro; 250!  ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[0]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[0.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16947.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/16947-shopymind-abandoned-cart-reminder.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges/></module><module><id><![CDATA[17545]]></id><name><![CDATA[veplatform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[VePlatform: Increase conversions from abandoned carts  ]]></displayName><description><![CDATA[Instantly increase your sales by adding the VePlatform&rsquo;s integrated remarketing and re-engagement apps that convert customers who abandon your site]]></description><description_full><![CDATA[Instantly increase your sales by adding the VePlatform&rsquo;s integrated remarketing and re-engagement apps that convert customers who abandon your site.  &nbsp;  Get connected to the VePlatform now!    &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[By integrating with the VePlatform you will have instant access to its suite of conversion enhancing remarketing and re-engagement apps designed to:     Improve your bounce rate   Increase customer engagement   Increase conversions by reducing abandonment   Generate higher ROI from your campaigns   Deliver incremental revenue    ]]></additional_description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></to></compatibility><nb_rates><![CDATA[0]]></nb_rates><avg_rate><![CDATA[0.0]]></avg_rate><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17545.jpg]]></img><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com//en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/17545-veplatform-increase-conversions-from-abandoned-carts.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/certif_prestashop_en.png]]></badge></badges></module></modules>
